Guide to the Radical and Labor Songbook Collection, circa 1850s-1980s.
Radical and Labor Songbook Collection,
- Individual song books, music sheets, periodical issues and broadsides, 1897-2013
  - S (2), 1942-1963 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Most Popular Songs from the Soviet Union, 1942; Stinson Trading Company (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - We Shall Overcome! Songs of the Northern Freedom Movement, 1963; Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee; Oak Publications (Box 4, Folder 6)
      4th Printing
  - S Oversized, 1911-1955 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Mamanu, or The Triangle Victims, 1911; Schorr, A.; Rumshisky, J.M.; Hebrew Publishing Co (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Come Place a Red Rose and My Loved One, 1955; Segal, Edith; Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - T, 1892-1930 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Songs, 1930; Textile Workers Organizing Committee of the C.I.O. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Labor Reform Songster, 1892; Thompson, Phillips; Journal of the Knights of Labor Print (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - T Oversized, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - The Defender of Cameron Dam, 1909; Trettin, Mrs. M.B.; Frederick Pollworth and Bro. Co (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Milwaukee, Wisconsin
  - U, 1940-1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - UAW-CIO Sings, 1941; UAW-CIO Education Department (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Labor Sings with the United Labor Party, 1954; Educational Department, United Labor Party of America (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Hootenanny Song Book, 1947; University of Michigan Chapter, American Veterans Committee (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Ann Arbor, Michigan
    - The School for Workers Song Book, 1941; University of Wisconsin School for Workers (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Song Book, 1940-1949; UOPWA - CIO (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Boycott Now, 1970-1979; UFW (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Canciones: UFW Songs, 1990-1999; El Taller Grafico (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - V, 1890-1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Official Souvenir Book (Libretto Officiale) commemorating the first American tour of the National Fascist Militia Band, 1934; Valenti, Domenico; Artcraft (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Venceremos Cantando: Songs of Struggle / Canciones de Lucha, 1976; 8th and 9th Contingents of the Venceremos Brigade (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Revised edition
    - The Alliance and Labor Songster, a Collection of Labor and Comic Songs, for the Use of Alliances, Debating Clubs, Political Gatherings, 1890; Vincent, Leopold; H.andL. Vincent (Box 5, Folder 1)
      4th edition, expanded. Later printing.
      Winfield, Kansas
  - V Oversized, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - We Have Fed You All a Thousand Years, 1918; Von Liebich, Rudolph; I.W.W. Education Bureau (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Credit for the poem is given to "Unknown Proletarian"
  - W (1), 1937-1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Songs for Southern Workers, 1973; West, Don; Appalachian Movement Press (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Facsimile edition
      Huntington, West Virginia
    - Southern Mountain Folk Tradition and the Folksong "Stars" Syndrome, 1971; West, Don; Appalachian Movement Press (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Songs for Southern Workers, 1978; West, Don; Appalachian Movement Press (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Farmers Union Songs, 1940-1949; Williams Sisters Harmony Trio; Journal Printers (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Fairbury, Nebraska
    - Songs of Witness, Undated; Witness for Peace (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Songs of the People, 1937; Workers Library Publishers (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - W (2), 1925-1947 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Two Slav Youth Songs: The Two Year Plan (Czechoslovakia) [and] The Youth Railway (Yugoslavia), 1947; Workers' Music Association Ltd. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Workers Song Book 1934 No. 1, 1934; Workers Music League (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Workers Songbook 2, 1935; Workers Music League (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - May Day Song Book, 1945; Workers Party and Labor Action (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Sing! Labor and Socialist Songs, 1945; Workers Party (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Sing!, 1940-1949; Workers Party and Young Peoples Socialist League (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Palkkaorjain Lauluja, 1925; Workers Society (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Duluth, Minnesota
    - Commonwealth Serenade Orchestra Ernst Hoffman conducting and American Folk Singers Thomas Johnson conducting, 1937; Works Progress Administration Federal Music Project (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Cambridge, Massachusetts
  - W Oversized, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Battle Hymn of Lt. Calley, 1971; Wilson, Julian; Smith, James M.; Shelby Singleton Music (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Nashville, Tennessee
  - Y, 1938-1972 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Young People's Socialist League Song Book, 1939; Young People's Socialist League (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Tenth National Convention
    - Young People's Socialist League Song Book, 1946; Young People's Socialist League (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Jacobin Songs: May Day - 1941, 1941; Young People's Socialist League - Jacobin Unit (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Staten Island, New Yotk
    - Songs for a Warless World, 1938; Youth Committee Against War (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - The Zippie Hymnal, 1972; Youth International Party; Zip (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Songbook series, 1940-1969
  - Broadside, 1962-1969
    - Broadside No. 1-12, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Broadside No. 13-18, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Broadside No. 19-23, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Broadside No. 24-28, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Broadside No. 30-36, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Broadside No. 37-42, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Broadside No. 43-49, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Broadside No. 100-101, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Promenade, 1940-1953
    - Promenade v. 1, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Promenade v. 1 no. 1, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Promenade v. 1 no. 8, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Promenade v. 1 no. 9, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Promenade v. 1 no. 10, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Promenade v. 3-4, 1942-1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Promenade v. 3 no. 9, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Promenade v. 4 no. 9, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Promenade v. 4 no. 10, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Promenade v. 5, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Promenade v. 5 no. 1, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Promenade v. 5 no. 2-3, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Promenade v. 5 no. 4, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Promenade v. 5 no. 5-7, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Promenade v. 5 no. 8-10, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Promenade v. 6, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Promenade v. 6 no. 1, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Promenade v. 6 no. 3, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Promenade v. 6 no. 4-5, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Promenade v. 6 no. 6, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Promenade v. 6 no. 7-9, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Promenade v. 6 no. 10, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Promenade v. 7, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Promenade v. 7 no. 1, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Promenade v. 7 no. 2, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Promenade v. 7 no. 3-5, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Promenade v. 7 no. 8, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Promenade v. 7 no. 9, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Promenade v. 7 no. 10, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Promenade v. 8, 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Promenade v. 8 no. 1, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Promenade v. 8 no. 2, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Promenade v. 8 no. 3, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Promenade v. 8 no. 4, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Promenade v. 8 no. 5, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Promenade v. 8 no. 6, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Promenade v. 8 no. 7, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Promenade v. 8 no. 8, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Sing Out!, 1950-1956
    - Sing Out! v. 1 no. 1-12, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Sing Out! v. 2 no. 1-12, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Sing Out! v. 3 no. 1-12, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Sing Out! v. 4 no. 1-7, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Sing Out! v. 5 no. 2-4, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Sing Out! v. 6 no. 2-3, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 12)